colocrossing.com 2019-07-02

# COLOCROSSING PRIVACY POLICY

COLOCROSSING PRIVACY POLICY
ColoCrossing (“ColoCrossing” or the “Company”) has a long-standing policy of protecting
the privacy of its Subscribers.
ColoCrossing believes that each Subscriber should know what information ColoCrossing
collects from them, as well as how that information is used, disclosed, and protected.
ColoCrossing has created this Policy statement to explain its privacy practices when you
visit or make a purchase from www.colocrossing.com. It will notify you of the following:
    1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Site, how it
         is used and with whom it may be shared.
    2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
    3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
    4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
ColoCrossing will not sell or disclose the personal information of any Subscribers to
unaffiliated third parties without your consent except as otherwise provided in this Policy, its
Terms of Service and its Acceptable Use Policy. ColoCrossing may use information about a
Subscriber’s identity, where and when a Subscriber browses on our Site, where a
Subscriber’s wireless device is located, and how a Subscriber uses its network in order for
ColoCrossing to provide each Subscriber with better service and to enrich each
Subscriber’s user experience when they sign up or use any of ColoCrossing’s Services.
Any terms not herein defined shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the ColoCrossing
Terms of Service.
COVERAGE OF THIS POLICY
This privacy policy includes colocrossing.com, chicagovps.net and hudsonvalleyhost.com
and all their subdomains within.
PURCHASE INFORMATION
We request information from you on our order form and, in order to buy from us, you must
provide information such as name and shipping address and financial information such as
credit card number and expiration date. This information is collected and used for billing
purposes and to complete your order. If there is an issue filling your order, we may use that
information to contact you. When you place an order through the site, we will maintain that
information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete the information. Should the

information you provided has changed or need to be modified, you can either request that it
be modified from us or make the modifications yourself through our web site.
Additionally, we use your order information to:
    1. Communicate with you.
    2. Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud. And,
    3. When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with
         information or advertising relating to our products or services.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email to tell you about new products or
services or changes to this privacy policy.
LOG FILES
Like many other websites, ColoCrossing makes use of log files (“Log Files”). The
information inside the Log Files includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, the type of
browser, Internet Service Provider (“ISP”), a date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and
number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track a Subscriber’s movement
around the website and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such
information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
All of the same information recorded in Log Files is also transmitted to Google Analytics. No
personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. Subscribers may opt out of
Google's advertising tracking cookie or a browser plugin to opt out of all Google Analytics
tracking software by clicking on the links provided.
COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS
ColoCrossing does use cookies to store information about Subscriber preferences, record
Subscriber-specific information on which pages the Subscriber accesses or visits,
customize webpage content based on a Subscriber’s browser type or other information that
a Subscriber sends via their browser. If a Subscriber wishes to disable cookies, they may
do so through their individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie
management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

ADVERTISING
The ColoCrossing website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies
are small data files that are stored on a Subscriber’s device. The ColoCrossing website
uses cookies dropped by ColoCrossing or third parties for a variety of purposes including to
operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may be used to track how a Subscriber
uses the website to target ads to the Subscriber on other websites. Upon visiting
ColoCrossing, a Subscriber will receive a tracking cookie which specifies if the Subscriber is
either a current client or only a visitor of the ColoCrossing website. This cookie is then used
on ColoCrossing’s advertising network(s) to provide the Subscriber with ads relevant to
them. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network
Advertising Initiative’s educational page at
http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
Facebook – https://www.facebook.com/settings
Google – https://www.google.com/settings/ads
Bing – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources
Further, you can opt out of some of these servicesby visiting the Digital Advertising
Alliance’s opt-out portal at http://optout.aboutads.info/.
INFORMATION SHARING
ColoCrossing only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside
of ColoCrossing in the following limited circumstances:
a. To subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the
purpose of processing personal information on the Company’s behalf. ColoCrossing
requires that these parties agree to process such information based on the Company’s
instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate
confidentiality and security measures the Company deems necessary;
b. If ColoCrossing has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of
such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal
process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service,
including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise
address fraud, security or technical issues or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property
or safety of ColoCrossing, its Subscribers or the public as required or permitted by law.

If ColoCrossing becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or
all of its assets, the Company will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information
involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred
and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
INFORMATION SECURITY
ColoCrossing takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access
to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data both on line and off line.
These include appropriate encryption, physical security and other necessary measures to
guard against unauthorized access to systems where the Company stores personal data.
For example, ColoCrossing restricts access to a Subscriber’s personal information to only
those ColoCrossing employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information
in order to process it on the Company’s behalf. These individuals are bound by
confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and
criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. Moreover, any personal data or
information that we transmit on line is encrypted.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
ColoCrossing will revise and update this Policy as it deems appropriate, including, for
example, if its practices change or if changes in the law so require. Subscribers should refer
back to this page periodically for the latest information.
Your Rights
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we have
on file about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated or
deleted. Additionally, if you are a European resident we emphasize that we are processing
your information in order to fulfill contracts that we have with you or otherwise pursuing
legitimate business interests previously outlined above.
For more information about our privacy practices please contact us a
sales@colocrossing.com or by mail at:
                                           ColoCrossing
                                       325 Delaware Avenue
                                         Buffalo, NY 14202
